digitalvidya.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy - Digital Vidya

### Privacy Policy

 **We are Committed to Privacy**

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices of Engaging Ideas Pvt Ltd, (owner of the brand Digital Vidya) for the website located at http://www.digitalvidya.com (the “Site”), related services, and Email communication to @digitalvidya.com and @digitalvidya.co.in domains, and other websites on the subdomain of www.digitalvidya.com, and its corporate affiliates (collectively, the “Service”).

Protecting your privacy is our top priority at Digital Vidya. Through this privacy policy, we aim to explain the ways in which your personal and business information is collected, used and protected at Digital Vidya. This privacy policy is a part of our [Terms of Use.](https://www.digitalvidya.com/terms-of-use/)

By visiting the website of Digital Vidya, we take it as consent to collect your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and also take it as acceptance from your end. we assure you that we do not sell, rent, transfer your information to any third party in any way than what is stated in the Privacy Policy.

You must understand that our services may be associated with certain other third parties as well, and the conditions and privacy like online storage services and payment providers, and you agree that Digital Vidya is not responsible for any such third party terms and conditions and their use of any of your information. This policy is strictly with the use of information collected by Digital Vidya.

**What information do we collect?**

On our website, we collect two types of information:

  1. Personally Identifiable Information (PII) such as Name, Email Id, Phone No and Company Name.
  2.  Non-PII which doesn’t reveal the identity of the visitor on our site. This includes :

**IP Addresses**

Digital Vidya automatically tracks your IP addresses. Your IP addresses are registered for statistical purposes and in order to improve our advertising and layout of our Website.

**Correspondence Information  **

If you send us any personal correspondence, or any third parties send us any form of information about your postings, the information may get stored on our servers.

**Payment Information**

We do not collect any credit card information to protect you against any unauthorized transactions. claims and other liabilities. We allow third-party vendors to collect information for the purpose of collecting the fee from our customers on our website. We do not have any access to the payment information that you provide to our third party vendors and all this information provided is subject to the privacy policy and the terms and conditions of the third party vendor. For more information, you may want to read the terms and conditions and the privacy policy of our payment service providers.

**How will we use the information we collect?**

  * The information we collect on our website will only be used by us to provide the requested information to the user or to update the user about our products and services.

**How is the information stored?**

Your information is saved in our database in order to improve our usee and website experience. Digital Vidya is an Indian company and if you choose to furnish any form of information to our servers. Since India doesn’t have a similar policy as present in other countries, we will protect it in a manner disclosed in our Privacy Policy. By visiting our website and providing us with your information, you understand and consent to this privacy policy. Your information may be transferred, processed and stored in India.

**How your information is protected**

You agree that Digital Vidya and its associated companies may use the Information for marketing and promotional purposes.

  * All our employees, independent contractors, and agents have executed non-disclosure agreements, which provide explicit confidentiality protections. Any employee, independent contractor or agent who violates such privacy and/or security policies is subject to possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.
  * We do not make any of your Information available to third parties for their marketing purposes. No data given or collected is shared with other social media platforms.
  * If however, we share your Business Information with third parties, we will notify you. Please note that no transmission over the internet can guarantee confidentiality and non-disclosure, and as such, you transmit at your own risk.
  * We use robust security measures to protect data from unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and help ensure the appropriate use of data. When the Services are accessed using the internet, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects your Information, using both server authentication and data encryption. These technologies help ensure that your Information is safe, secure, and only available to you and to whom you have granted access.
  * We do not tolerate Spam. To report Digital Vidya related spam, please contact us at info@digitalvidya.com. You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our terms of use. We may check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks, and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content of the Website, but we will not permanently store messages sent through these tools.
  * Digital Vidya does its utmost to secure communications and data storage in order to protect the confidentiality of your Information against loss and interception by third parties. However, it is important to know that there is no zero-risk against loss or interception by others of your Information. You are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of your Account’s username and password.

**Cookies Policy  **

Digital Vidya uses cookies to give you a great browsing experience. Whenever you visit our website, our server sends a cookie to your device in order to determine your location and use an appropriate language for you. You are free to delete these cookies at any time.  Cookies do not have the capacity to personally identify an individual and they can at the most merely identify the web browser. Unless an individual chooses to identify himself by opening an account or entering login information, the user will remain anonymous to us.

**Legal Requests**

We comply with all legal requirements and co-operate with law enforcement agencies as well as third parties to enforce laws, safeguard intellectual property rights and prevent fraud. If we are furnished with a legal order by any governmental or law enforcement agency, we shall disclose your name, e-mail address and website usage history, on your authorization, with or without a legal order. We will not disclose any of your other information to any agency without a court order except when it becomes necessary for any safety, security or a similar concern. 

**Disclosure of information to any third party**

We will not share your information to any third party without prior consent from you.

Consent

**Consent**

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of your Information as described in this Privacy Policy and our [terms of use](https://www.digitalvidya.com/terms-of-use/). 

**Third Party Links**

Our website may contain links to other websites which are not owned or controlled by us. We bear no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these third-party sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personal information. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this Website.

**Changes**

If our Privacy Policy procedures change, we will post those changes immediately to our Website. Any such changes will be effective immediately from the time they are posted unless otherwise stated in the change provision. An email notification will be sent to the users who request it.

**Your Rights**

Under the EU  **General Data Protection Regulation(GDPR)** , you possess a number of rights in relation to your Personal Data. You have right to access your personal information from the website for any purpose. You can get and reuse your personal information across any services at any time. Whereas you have provided us with consent, you have the right to withdraw this consent at any time. To reiterate, you can do this at any time by contacting us directly at info@digitalvidya.com

**How to modify the information or opt-out of updates?**

  * You may use the following options for removing your information from our email database if you wish to opt out of receiving promotional emails and newsletters.
  * Click on the “unsubscribe” link on the bottom of the email.
  * Click on the “Account Settings” link from the site home page, and un-check the undesired promotions.
  * Send mail to the following postal address letting us know which promotional emails you wish to opt-out of:  
Engaging Ideas Pvt Ltd, 1001-1002, 10th Floor, Tower-1, Pearls Omaxe Building, Netaji Subhash Place, Pitampura, New Delhi – 110034

Attn: Customer Service
